

Jasmin Shukla Laravel Devloper

Highly skilled and motivated web development engineer with 6+ years of experience. I am an excellent team worker and am able to take instructions from all levels and build up good working relationships with all colleagues. I am flexible, reliable and possess excellent time keeping skills.



♥ PHONE



mr.jasmin.shukal@gmail.com



2016-2018

2014-2016

Expertise











Languages





Education

BCA

Saurashtra University

Industrial Training Institute

Copa, Computer Science

Work experience

App Gurus, Australia

Mar 2022 — Till Now

Sr.Laravel Developer

Team communication|Team performance control | Bug fixing Code cleanup and refactoring | Work on new application features

Anant Soft Computing

Dec 2020 — Feb 2022

Sr.Laravel Developer

Bug fixing |Code cleanup and refactoring | Work on new website features

Zetta 10

Mar 2020 — Dec 2020

Laravel Developer

Working with the wider development team. | Manage website design, development, api | Development | PWA

Smart WebTech

Aug 2018 — Feb 2020

Jr.PHP Developer

Creating Web Service, Web portals, Admin Panels | Backend Development

Binary Bits

Feb 2018 — Jul 2018

Jr. PHP Developer

Website, Admin Panels | Learn New Technology

Raj Design

Feb 2017 — Feb 2018

Jr. PHP Developer

Creating Web Pages | Design in PhotoShop and Al.